tweetdelete.net 2019-05-30

# TweetDelete - Privacy policy

## Privacy Policy

This policy describes how we hold and process your private information. It applies to the free services Tweetails, TweetDownload and TweetDelete that are operated by Richard West Ltd.

### Overview

We collect the minimum amount of personal information necessary for our services to function. This is processed with your consent, or on another legal basis. We don't sell any information to third parties, and we only use it as this privacy policy describes.

### What information we collect and why

We collect various information related to your Twitter account from users who sign in to our website, such as your Twitter user ID, Twitter screen name, and access keys for the Twitter API.  
_Why we collect this:_ We need these details for our Twitter related services to function, and so that we can use Twitter API functions on your behalf in order to provide our services on your Twitter account.

We collect or process certain additional data contained in your Twitter account (which could potentially contain sensitive data) where the functionality our service is providing requires it. This could include your tweets or your direct messages.  
_Why we collect this:_ We only collect this type of data in order to provide a service you've asked us to. We're careful to only hold it for as long as necessary - for example TweetDelete needs to scan your tweets to work out which to delete, but they are used temporarily and never stored in our database.

We collect various information about visitors to our website due to our use of common internet technologies such as web server logs. This includes details like the visitor's browser type, language preference, referring site, additional websites requested, and the date and time of each visitor request. We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.  
_Why we collect this:_ We collect this information to understand how visitors use our websites, and to monitor and protect the security and stability of our websites.

We do not intentionally collect sensitive categories of data. Because we process social media posts, there are situations where such data may pass through our service without our knowledge.

### How we share the information we collect

We do not sell any information to third parties. We do not share any information with third parties unless a service you've requested necessitates this (for example if you want to share your results page on Tweetails). 

### Global privacy practices

We store and process the information that we collect in the United Kingdom in accordance with this privacy policy. All data is processed fairly and lawfully in accordance with UK and EU law and the principles and requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 ("the GDPR").

### Our legal basis for processing information

We only process personal data for lawful purposes as described in Article 6 of the GDPR. For all of the main functionality of our services our legal basis is that you've given us consent to access this information in order to provide a particular service related to your Twitter account.

Generally, the remainder of the processing of personal data we perform is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests. For example, the information stored by us in web server logs is necessary for us to monitor the security and stability of our websites.

### Right of access

You can contact us using the details below at any time to request a copy of any data associated with you that we hold.

### Right to erasure

You can contact us using the details below at any time to request the deletion of any data associated with you that we hold.

### Contacting us

For any matters related to data protection, you can contact us via email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#f3809681859a909680b3909f969281909b929c80dd909c9e) or write to Richard West Ltd, 49 Gaunt Street, Lincoln, LN5 7PU, UK. For specific data access/deletion requests, please include your Twitter account name and let us know which of our services your request relates to.

If we've missed anything or if you have any specific questions or concerns, please get in touch. We're a small company, but we take user privacy very seriously.
